

About Me

I am a **software developer** with three years of experience. I've built multiple full-stack mobile & web applications. I have collaborated with clients to enhance and build software applications. I am seeking a role as **React Developer** to continue my passion for building things.

Education

University of Montana

Management Information Systems Aug 2013 - Jan 2018

Skills

ReactJs (React & React Native) HTML, CSS (SCSS) SQL

Visual Basic Java Python

C# (In Progress)

Interest



Work Experience

Technology Specialist

People's Voice On Climate Jan 2021 – Present

- Designed and launched multiple email marketing campaigns with Mailchimp.
- Redesigned UI of company website.
- Configured users permissions and managed finances through Google Workspace Admin.

Implementation Consultant

Fast Enterprises Sep 2019 – Oct 2020

- Collaborated with a 3rd party vendor to implement a system to process taxpayer data.
- Implemented an electronic filing service that processes tax returns.
- Created data reports, presented demos to clients, and wrote guides and documentation.

IT Analyst

Fantasy Moguls May 2018 – Oct 2018

- Automated the process to retrieve the most up-to-date roster.
- Analyzed the top paying users for asset management.

App Developer

UM School of Business Sep 2017 – Dec 2017

- Designed, and developed an Android application to collect student data entries.
- Led Scrum meetings with the client to review functional specifications and designs.

Related Projects

Softlete

Aug 2021 - Present
A full stack **React** application



Try it

Habts

Feb 2021 - Present A full stack **React** application



See More

Athletics/Affiliations

Sports Performance Trainer

Freelance Spring 2021 - Present

Professional Athlete & Coach

MSA Tigers Football Team (Cairo, Egypt)

Feb 2019 – May 2019

Collegiate Athlete

University of Montana Football Team

Aug 2013 - Dec 2017